Gabi! More coffee!
加比  再来点咖啡
I haven't slept in two days.
我两天没睡了
Sounds like somebody's getting lucky.
看来某人很走运啊
That puts the "nasty" in "doing the nasty."
真是肮脏人做肮脏事啊
Sex with Alan is wild.
和埃兰的性爱很狂野
I feel like Elliot, Queen of the Jungle.
我感觉自己是丛林女王艾略特
Last night we did it in the craziest place...
昨晚我们在一个特别疯狂的地方做了
the bedroom floor.
卧室地板上
Oh please, I've done it on the floor
拜托  我在卫浴寝具批发商城的
of Bed, Bath & Beyond.
地板上做过
I went in with a 20% off coupon,
我带着八折优惠券进去
and got 100% off.
结果他们免单了
So...
话说...
Before my amazing girlfriend comes down, I need your help.
在我超棒的女朋友下来之前  我需要你的帮助
Shauna is being honored
旧金山记者协会
by the San Francisco Journalists Association,
要给肖娜颁奖
and I need to think of an awesome gift.
我得想出一个超棒的礼物
Oh, and...
还有
ferris wheel.
摩天轮
Oh, look at me.
瞧瞧我
I'm rich. I can buy a ferris wheel.
哥有钱  买得起摩天轮
I was talking about the craziest place I ever had sex.
我是说我最疯狂的做爱地点
In a ferris wheel
在摩天轮上
at a wedding with a carnival theme.
婚礼现场  是嘉年华主题
Beat that.
谁有我牛
I can.
我有
My daughter's seventh birthday
我女儿七岁生日时
in the bouncy castle
在充气城堡里
with the clown.
和小丑来了一发
It turns out noses aren't
原来小丑们
the only thing clowns like to honk.
喜欢捏的不只是鼻子
Kids, clowns, hetero sex--
孩子  小丑  异性性行为
there's nothing for me here.
这里没我事了
You have another kid... besides Brett?
除了布雷特...你还有个孩子吗
Yeah, Danielle, she's 25.
是啊  丹妮尔  她25岁了
Two kids.
两个孩子
Is that it?
没别的了吧
I don't talk about Danielle that often.
我不常说起丹妮尔
Unfortunately, we haven't spoken in years.
不幸的是  我们很多年没说过话了
What? A mother-daughter not close? What happened?
什么  母女不睦吗  出了什么事
Gabi, sounds like it's kind of a private thing.
加比  这听起来像是私事
Yeah, yeah, that's why I'm asking.
是啊  所以我才问
It's okay, Josh.
没事  乔什
I was a child myself when I had her.
我怀她是自己也是个孩子
And if I'm truthful, I think we're just too much alike.
要是说实话  我觉得我们太像了
Now can we talk about breakfast?
现在我们可以说说早餐了吗
Yes. Would you like eggs?
是的  你想吃蛋吗
And do you at least send each other Christmas cards?
你们互相发圣诞卡片吗
Well, I do. I just-- I never get one back.
我发的  但她没有回过我
Not even an E-card?
电子贺卡都没吗
But they're free.
那是免费的呀
Last I heard,
最近一次的消息
she was making artisanal maple syrup in Vermont.
是她在佛蒙特州做手工枫糖浆
Now if you'll excuse me, I'm off to go cry in my car.
我先失陪了  要去车里哭了
- Shauna! - I'm just kidding. A driver's picking me up.
-肖娜  -我开玩笑的  有司机来接我
I'm gonna cry in his car.
我要去他的车里哭
Hey, you know what a great gift for Shauna would be?
你知道给肖娜什么礼物好吗
A therapist... thanks to you.
心理医生  多谢了你
No. Get her and her daughter back together.
不  让她和她女儿团聚
No, that's Shauna's personal business.
不  那是肖娜的私事
- It's not my place to get involved. - Yeah, that's why
-我不该插手  -是啊  所以
it would be such a great surprise-- she'd never see it coming.
这会是个很棒的惊喜  她不会料到的
Every mother and daughter want to be close.
每个母亲和女儿都想亲密
Come on, Josh, trust me.
拜托  乔什  相信我
Trust you? No.
相信你吗  不
- But-- - No!
-但是  -不
- Is that a firm-- - Yes!
-那是坚定的...  -是的
- So that's a yes! - No!
-你同意了  -不
No!
不行
- Just-- - No.
-就...  -不行
Okay.
好吧
Oh my damn.
我的妈呀
A pig in a blanket.
毯子下面藏着头猪
I don't know what happened.
我不知道怎么回事
I came to get Josh's tux for the cleaner's,
我进来拿乔什要送去干洗的西装
I smelled his pillow, and the next thing I know--
闻到了他枕头的气味  于是我就...
Okay, night-night.
晚安好梦
Okay, baby, something definitely isn't right.
好了  亲爱的  肯定出什么事了
Come on. I don't usually put you down for your nap until 4:00.
快起来  以前我四点才哄你午睡的
I spent my first weekend at Alan's place and couldn't sleep,
我第一次在埃兰家过周末  根本睡不着
'cause I was afraid I might do something embarrassing.
因为我怕自己出丑
It can't be more embarrassing than what you do when you're awake.
没什么比你醒着的时候做的事更囧的了
Hey, I just got an idea.
我想到一个办法
Can you come over to my house and watch me sleep?
你能来我家看我睡觉吗
I would, but The Exorcist is on,
我也想  但是正在放《驱魔人》
and watching that sounds a little less scary.
看它都没看你睡觉吓人
I can get you front-row seats to see Usher!
我能帮你弄到亚瑟小子演唱会的前排票
I'm gonna need your address, a key, and some holy water.
给我你家地址  钥匙  备好圣水
Hey, Josh, I made you a little snack--
乔什  我给你做了点点心
chicken and waffles.
炸鸡配华夫饼
No, thank you. I'm not hungry.
不  谢谢  我不饿
"Where's the maple syrup," you say?
你是问"枫糖浆在哪"吗
I didn't say.
我没问
What are you saying?
你这话是什么意思
I'm just saying the syrup's on the way over...
我是说糖浆在从佛蒙特州
from Vermont.
来这里的路上
- You didn't. - I did.
-你不是吧  -是的
I called Danielle, and she really wants to see her mom.
我给丹妮尔打了电话  她非常想见她妈妈
I know you told me not to, but it was the right thing to do.
我知道你让我别这么做  但这是对的
- I had to! - Gabi, call it off.
-我必须这么做  -加比  取消见面
Too late.
太晚了
Shauna, would you come down here, please?
肖娜  能下来一下吗
How dare you! I clearly said no.
你胆子真大  我明明说了不行
There were no other words surrounding it. One word. "No."
都没别的话  就一句"不行"
What's all the commotion?
吵什么呢
Shauna, I want you to know
肖娜  我希望你明白
I had nothing to do with this.
这件事跟我毫无关系
Hi, mom.
你好  妈妈
Oh my God! Dani!
天呐  丹妮
What are you doing here?
你来这里干什么
Well, she flew all the way across the country
她飞过整个美国
because she wanted to see you. Isn't that right, Danielle?
就因为她想见你  对吗  丹妮尔
When Gabi called me, I jumped at the chance.
加比给我打电话的时候  我就决定来了
And you wanna know why she never sent you any cards?
你想知道她为什么从不给你寄贺卡吗
Well, you tell her.
你说吧
- It's-- it's-- - She really needed her independence,
-因为...  -她非常想要独立
but now she realizes that-- you tell her.
但现在她意识到...  你说吧
My life is nowhere near as good without you in it.
没有你的生活一点都不美妙
Can you ever forgive me?
你能原谅我吗
Can I?
我能吗
She can. She can.
她能  她能
See, Josh? I told you this would all work out.
乔什 看到没  跟你说这办法管用吧
Now, if you wanna pay me back for her plane ticket,
要是你想帮我报销她的机票钱
- that would be really great. - Not cool.
-就再好不过了  -糟了
This is totally not cool. This is a disaster.
出大事了  这简直是场灾难
Seriously? Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
真的吗  我们看到的是一回事吗
Because what I'm seeing is a beautiful mother-daughter reunion
因为我看到的是一幅在我们面前
happening right in front of us.
母女重聚的温馨景象
What could possibly be wrong with this picture?
这种情况下会出什么问题啊
That's ferris-wheel girl!
她就是摩天轮女孩
Are you sure that's ferris-wheel girl?
你确定那就是摩天轮女孩吗
I mean, it was years ago in the dark.
那都是几年前的漆黑夜晚了
Dark? She was all lit up.
"漆黑"吗  她整个人都是亮的
Her body was red, then blue,
她身上一会红  一会蓝
then yellow... then red again.
一会黄...  然后又变成红色的了
Well, maybe she won't remember you.
或许她不记得你了
Come on, Gabi. It's me!
得了吧  加比  是我哎
Josh, I'm so excited to say this,
乔什  我太激动了
meet my daughter Danielle.
认识一下我的女儿丹妮尔
Hi, I'm Josh.
你好  我叫乔什
Hey, nice to meet you.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you, too.
我也很高兴见到你
- Well, this calls for champagne. - Great idea!
-这时候该来杯香槟  -好主意
Oh! I'm sorry, Dani. It's Anderson Cooper.
抱歉  丹妮  是安德森·库珀打来的
He gets real whiny if you don't pick up. I'll be right back.
要是不接他会发牢骚  我马上回来
So... maple syrup, huh?
枫糖浆是吧
Yeah, it's kinda random, but it suits me.
是的  也是机缘巧合  但挺适合我
Vermont!
佛蒙特州
Pretty cold there. Gets kind of cold there in the winter.
那里挺冷的  冬天冰天雪地
Yeah. Way to cold to have sex on a ferris wheel.
是啊  冷得没办法在摩天轮上嘿咻
I knew it! I knew you remembered me!
我就知道  我知道你记得我
Yeah, who could forget? You were red,
当然  谁忘得了  你一会红
then blue, then yellow, and then red again.
一会蓝  一会黄  然后又变成红色的了
- Champagne is served. - It's her. I told you.
-香槟来了  -就是她  我说了吧
You're ferris-wheel girl?
你是摩天轮女孩吗
Damn it!
该死
Do you see what you did?
看看你都做了些什么
Do you see what you did
你都做了些什么
when you did the thing I told you not to do?
我叫你不要做你非要做的事情
Well, if you didn't do the thing that you shouldn't have done,
要是你没做你不该做的事情
then the thing I did
那么我做的这事
would've been the thing that I should've done!
就会变成我该做的了
So what are we gonna do?
我们现在怎么办
Okay, everybody just shut up, all right?
大家别吵了  好吗
This is a very precious day.
今天是个宝贵的日子
You know what you did to him.
你知道你对他做了什么
He knows what he did to you. The important thing is
他知道他对你做了什么  关键是
your mother can never find out what you did to each other.
绝不能让你妈妈知道你们之间做的事
You want me to lie to Shauna?
你想让我欺骗肖娜吗
That puts me in a very uncomfortable position.
我会很难受的
Oh, really? Well, it can't be any more uncomfortable
是吗  总不会比你们俩
than the position you guys were in on the ferris wheel!
在摩天轮上更难受了吧
Gabi, this dinner was absolutely delicious.
加比  晚餐太美味了
And completely uneventful.
而且非常顺利
Mom, do you realize
妈妈  你发现
this is the first dinner we've had together in three years?
这是三年来我俩第一次共进晚餐吗
- To making up for lost time. - Cheers!
-为了补偿失去的时光  -干杯
Well, get ready, 'cause now it's time
准备好  因为此时此刻
for the first dessert you've had together in three years.
该是三年来你们俩第一次一起品尝甜品了
I'm so happy.
我好高兴
Oh, don't worry, Shauna. I've got it.
没事的  肖娜  我来收拾吧
I insist. You've done so much for me.
让我来吧  你为我做的已经太多了
Thanks.
谢谢
I mean, this is a miracle.
这真是个奇迹
- Things are going great. - I know.
-一切都太顺利了  -我知道
- She doesn't have a clue. - Well, thank God.
-她什么都不知道  -太好了
- I really like your mom. - Yeah, she's great.
-我真的很喜欢你妈妈  -是啊  她棒极了
I love her... so much,
我真的很爱她
- and you know what? - What?
-还有  你知道吗  -知道什么
I love you, too.
我也爱你
I've thought about you every single night
自从我们在摩天轮上嘿咻以后
ever since we made love on that ferris wheel.
我每天晚上都在想着你
It just keeps going round and round in my mind,
那幕一直在我脑海中转啊转
- like a... - I don't know-- ferris wheel?
-就像...  -就像摩天轮一样吗
Yes! That's it!
没错  就是这样
You totally get me,
你太懂我了
and now here I am,
如今我在这里
sitting next to you. It's like...
坐在你身边  就像是...
destiny!
命中注定
- Who's ready for dessert on the terrace? - I am, mommy!
-谁想去阳台上吃甜点  -我想  妈妈
Oh, and can you make some hot cocoa?
还有  能帮我做点热巧克力吗
Anything for you, darling.
什么都行  亲爱的
I thought she'd never leave.
她真是阴魂不散
What is wrong with you? You're acting crazy!
你是怎么了  简直像疯了一样
No, I am not.
不  我没有
I just wanna bite your neck!
我只是好想在你脖子上种草莓
- I'll be outside! - We'll be outside!
-我先出去了  -我也去
Perfect timing. I've got the dessert.
时间刚刚好  甜品也准备好了
Gabi, we have a problem.
加比  麻烦大了
- Danielle's in love with me. - What? Why would you think that?
-丹妮尔爱上我了  -你怎么会这么想
She said, "I love you," she's never stopped loving me...
她说了"我爱你"  一直爱着我
- She wants to bite my neck. - I see what's going on here.
-她想在我脖子上种草莓  -我明白了
You're just upset because I went against your wishes,
你只是不高兴我不按你说的做
it all worked out, and you can't stand it.
而一切又这么顺利  所以你无法接受
Gabi, is the water warm yet for Danielle's cocoa?
加比  给丹妮尔冲热巧克力的水开了吗
Everything's ready to go.
一切都准备好了
Here you go.
给你
Go! Go!
去吧  快去啊
Oh, you forgot the marshmallows.
你忘了拿棉花糖
No, no, no, no. Don't go.
不不不  别走啊
Hi.
你好啊
Okay, look, this has to stop.
你不能再这样了
You're right. No, you're right.
没错  你说得对
I came here to fix my relationship with my mother,
我是来修复和妈妈的关系的
so this can't happen.
所以我们不能这样
- Thank you. - But this can.
-谢谢你  -但这个可以
Oh god!
天啊
I'm just so happy that you and Danielle are back together!
真高兴能看到你跟丹妮尔重聚
Me too. You're smushing the marshmallows, darling.
我也是  但你快把棉花糖挤坏了  亲爱的
Oh, the actual marshmallows.
原来你说的不是胸
Hey, you found the marshmallows. Awesome.
你找到棉花糖了  真棒
I just noticed the time. I've got to get down to the studio.
原来已经这么晚了  我得去演播室了
I'm on air tonight.
我今晚有节目
- Josh, I trust you'll entertain my daughter while I'm out. - No!
-乔什  你会帮我好好招待女儿的对吗  -不
I mean... Gabi?
我的意思是...  加比
Uh, I was thinking, since you have to work,
我在想  既然你要工作
maybe Danielle should come with me and spend the night at my place.
或许丹妮尔今晚可以去我那  跟我住
- Great idea. - Yes.
-这主意不错  -太棒了
No!
不
I... just don't want to be any trouble.
我只是不想太麻烦你们
Really?
真的吗
I mean, yeah, that's no trouble at all.
没事的  一点都不麻烦
Yeah, you girls run and have some fun.
对啊  你们女生好好去玩玩吧
Maybe meet some boys. Come on, darling.
见见帅哥什么的  去吧  亲爱的
You've been stuck in the woods of Vermont.
你一直待在佛蒙特那种乡下地方
When was the last time you went and got crazy?
有多久都没出去好好疯狂一番了
Okay, let's go.
好了  咱们走
Okay, let's do this.
我准备好了  来吧
Oh my god! How did you make those pajamas?
老天  你这睡衣是什么做的
Did you skin an entire zoo?
剥了整间动物园的皮吗
I like your pajamas, too.
我也挺喜欢你的睡衣
Did it come with Barbie, or was it sold separately?
是跟芭比娃娃一起卖的  还是可以单买
Which bed do you sleep in?
你睡的是哪张床
That's Fluffykins' bed.
那是毛球的床
He turns in late, after Law & Order.
他睡得比较晚  要等《法律与秩序》播完以后
What are you doing? I need you in the bed,
你在做什么  我要你睡到床上来
so I can simulate having a person next to me while I sleep.
这样我才能假装有人睡在我身边
I'm not simulating anything!
我才不要跟你假装什么
You know what? Forget this whole thing.
知道吗  老娘不干了
I got you tickets to Usher. We had a deal!
我给你弄到了亚瑟小子的票  我们说好了的
Fine! But I'm building a pillow wall.
好吧  那我要用枕头堆座墙
Getting into bed with a man and not touching him.
跟一个男人同床共枕却不能碰
It's like I'm married all over again.
就跟老娘当年结婚时一模一样
She was kissing all over her mother's boyfriend?
她在狂亲她老妈的男朋友
Ooh! I saw this on a telenovela once.
我在浪漫肥皂剧里看过这桥段
Did she just come out of a coma?
她是刚刚从昏迷中苏醒吗
I don't want her to hear.
小声点  我不想让她听见
Don't worry about it. She's in the shower.
别担心  她在洗澡呢
I mean, the whole way over here
回来的这一路上
I was trying to convince her that if she went for Josh,
我都在劝她  如果她要勾引乔什
then she would ruin her relationship with her mother forever.
就会彻底毁了她跟她老妈的关系
And you know what she said?
你知道她说什么吗
"Josh tastes like cotton candy!"
"乔什尝起来像棉花糖"
I mean, she's here for two more days.
她还得在这待两天呢
- What am I gonna do? - Oh, no, no, you don't have two more days.
-我该怎么办  -不  你没时间了
That crazy bomb is ticking. You need to get rid of her now.
这疯女人随时都会爆发  你得赶紧弄走她
Or-- I mean, what if I pull out
或者  我可以
all the photo albums of me and my mother, I mean,
把我和妈妈的相册拿给她看
and show her what a real relationship looks like?
让她明白什么是真正的母女关系
I feel like that's what my mom's telling me to do.
我觉得这是我妈妈会想让我做的
Really? Listen again.
真的吗  你再好好听听
Because what I'm hearing is...
因为我觉得她说的是
"Drive that crazy bitch to the airport
"赶紧把那疯婆子送去机场
"and put her on a plane to Vermont."
让她坐飞机回佛蒙特去"
You know what? I think I'm gonna get out the photo albums,
知道吗  我还是去把相册拿出来
so when she gets out of the shower,
这样等她洗完澡出来
- then she's-- - Wait, wait, wait, wait.
-就可以...  -等等
She's been in there for forever.
她在里面待了好久
She should've run out of hot water 20 minutes ago.
热水应该二十分钟前就用光了
Oh god!
天呐
Oh god! Oh god! Oh god!
天呐  天呐  天呐
Maybe my mom really was talking to you,
或许你说的没错
because that crazy bitch climbed out the bathroom window!
那疯婆子居然从浴室窗户里爬出去了
Just like the telenovela.
就跟浪漫肥皂剧里一样
No, no, no, no, no!
不不不不
No! No!
不
Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
不不不不不
Danielle, stop!
丹妮尔  停下
Just because you once had sex with Josh on a ferris wheel,
就算你和乔什以前在摩天轮上嘿咻过
doesn't mean you can sneak into be with him now!
也不代表你现在能偷偷爬上他床啊
I can explain.
我可以解释
I asked you not to fly Shauna's daughter out here,
我让你不要把肖娜女儿接过来
but you did.
但你接了
And no one was supposed to tell Shauna
本来没人会告诉肖娜
that I had sex with her daughter,
我和她女儿上过床
but you did.
但你说了
Maybe it's gonna be okay.
或许会没事的呢
I mean, after she gets over her initial shock,
在度过最初的震惊期之后
Shauna's gonna be fine.
肖娜会没事的
Josh, these two weeks have been some of the best times I've ever had,
乔什  和你一起的这两周真的很愉快
and I never imagined it would come to such a humiliating end. Goodbye!
我真是没想到结局会是这么羞辱  再见
Shauna, wait.
肖娜  等等
Look... we all have pasts.
我们都有过去
The important thing is I wanna be with you.
重要的是我想和你在一起
No, you had sex with my daughter!
不  你睡了我女儿
What's that thing all the Americans say?
你们美国人怎么说的来着
Oh yeah. Eww!
对了  恶心
Oh, it's Danielle.
是丹妮尔的短信
"Mom, maple syrup emergency. Had to fly home.
"妈妈  枫糖厂出了急事  得回家了
So thrilled about you and Josh, and...
见到你和乔什在一起真高兴
I loved seeing you so happy. Kiss, hug, Danielle."
喜欢看你幸福的样子  亲亲抱抱  丹妮尔"
See? See? She chose you over Josh.
看到了吗  你和乔什她选了你
I did the right thing.
我做的很对
I guess, in a funny way, you did.
虽然可笑  但没错
Goodbye, Gabi.
再见  加比
Goodbye, Josh.
再见  乔什
Hugs are for people who haven't slept with my daughter.
我只抱没睡过我女儿的人
Why?
为什么
Why? Why?
为什么  为什么
Why? Why, why, why? Why?
为什么  为什么  为什么
Why? You know what? Don't answer that question!
为什么  你猜怎么着  不用回答
Get out!
请你出去
Out!
出去
Alan, I would say, "Rise and shine,"
埃兰  我想说"太阳晒屁股了"
but it appears somebody already has.
可在我屁股上的不是太阳嘛
I'm not Alan,
我不是埃兰
and that's one of my hair rollers!
那是我的发卷
Yolanda!
尤兰达
You were supposed to be watching me,
你该看着我睡觉的
not getting your woman stink on me.
不是沾我一身女人臭味
I'm sorry! I closed my eyes for one second,
对不起  我就闭了一下眼
next thing I know, I woke up spooning an Asian Danny DeVito!
美国演员  身高仅152
Wait, so you slept the whole night?
等等  所以你整晚都睡过去了吗
You didn't see me do anything?
没看我干了什么吗
Oh, relax! We both slept through the night.
放心  我们晚上都在睡觉
What's the weirdest thing that could've happened?
能发生什么奇怪的事
Wait. How did you get my--
等等  你怎么会...
And how did you manage to put on...
你又怎么穿了...
Why are you here? It can't be good.
你怎么会来  一定不是好事
Gabi, open the door.
加比  开门
Okay, first, let me start by saying I'm really, really sorry
首先  我要跟你说我真的对这一切
about everything, and to make it up to you,
很抱歉  为了补偿你
I made your favorite dish.
我做了你最喜欢的菜
- Truffle mac and cheese? - Your second favorite dish.
-松露奶酪通心粉吗  -你第二喜欢的
Sofia called me, and I know it was your mother's birthday this week.
索菲亚打电话给我  我知道这周是你妈妈的生日
And I think that explains your behavior yesterday.
这也就解释了你昨天的行为
Not every other day.
但不包括其他天的
I guess this time of year's really hard for me.
我猜每年的这个时候我都很难受
I want you to know my door's always open if you need to talk.
如果你想聊聊  我的门永远对你敞开
Not my bedroom door.
不是卧室门
I guess after you said, "Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?",
在你说了那么多"为什么"以后
it really made me think, "Why?"
让我也开始思考  为什么呢
And I realized I was just trying
然后我明白了我只是
to live vicariously through Danielle and Shauna.
想从丹妮尔和肖娜身上产生共鸣
I thought maybe if I could get them back together, then...
觉得如果我能让她俩团聚  那...
God, I would do anything to have one more moment with my mom.
天啊  能再和妈妈团聚我干什么都可以
I know...
我知道
which is why I'm giving you the rest of the week off
所以这周剩下的时间我给你放假
and sending you and Sofia on a little trip.
送你和索菲亚去玩一趟
What? Where are we going?
什么  去哪里
Let me... give you a little hint.
让我给你个小提示
Julia Child's kitchen in the Smithsonian?
史密森尼博物馆的茱莉亚·蔡尔德烹饪展吗
- My mom always wanted to take me here. - I know.
-妈妈一直想带我去的  -我知道
Sofia already packed your bags. She's meeting us at the airport.
索菲亚已经帮你收好了行李  她在机场等我们
Wait, wait, wait. I ruined your relationship,
等等  我毁了你的恋爱
and you're sending me on a free trip?
你还要让我免费旅游吗
I should not have mentioned that.
我不该提这茬的
At least let me give you the chicken parm that I made you.
至少让我给你为你做的芝士煎鸡排
Chicken parm? Not even top 10.
芝士鸡排  前十都不是好吗
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等  等等
One more thing.
还有件事
Thank you.
谢谢
Elliot, I have something to tell you.
艾略特  我有话要跟你说
- What? - I've been having a hard time sleeping next to you.
-什么  -我在你身边睡不着
I'm so worried that I might do something in my sleep
好担心睡梦中会做什么事
and you won't think I'm sexy anymore.
让你觉得我不性感了
- What? - I know.
-什么  -我知道
With this moneymaker, that's crazy.
我这么玉树临风  怎么可能
But what if?
但万一呢
You've been worried about that?
你在担心这个吗
I've been worried about the same thing!
我担心的也是这个
Oh please. You don't know from worry.
拜托  你有什么好担心的
I don't? I was so worried,
我当然有  我担心到
I paid Yolanda to watch me sleep.
花钱让尤兰达看我睡觉
That's so sweet!
你太贴心了
- Did you do anything weird? - No.
-你们做了什么奇怪的事吗  -没有
This is crazy. Who cares what we do in our sleep?
真是疯狂  谁在意我们怎么睡觉呢
We can be ourselves. We love each other.
我们可以做自己  我们那么相爱
- We do? - Well... I do.
-有吗  -我是的
I do too.
我也是
Good, because I have sleep apnea.
那就好  因为我有睡眠呼吸暂停症
Good night, sweetheart.
晚安  亲爱的
Oh, who cares?
管它呢